If you've seen my video 5 international designers you need to know you should be
familiar with the name corset factory professional and today I'm going to show
you an outfit from them because they sent me something after said video and
I'm really really happy that I can introduce this brand on my channel I've
got this posture collar and this dress and corset factory pro specializes in
PVC leather manufacturing. So this is really heavy and really high quality PVC fabric.
And before I am going to change into it I want to show you the inside because the inside is almost
like velvet. It's really really or the color is actually velvet and here we have some kind of
cotton lining. So the lining is also very high quality and very soft to the touch. I changed
into it and I decided to do the full look. I added some PVC gloves and some lace up PVC boots
because the skirt is so... the skirt part of the dress is the dress because that skirt part is so
long and it overlaps with the boots so basically no skin visible anymore. And what I also noticed
is that the skirt part is quite tight. There is not a lot of room so I can barely like move
really far with my legs. It's almost like kind of a hobble skirt. It's like making teeny tiny steps
and also can't really lift the legs up. So this is the max which also kind of adds to the restrictive
nature of the dress as well as the really high and tight collar and I love
the overall look because it's really smooth really glossy and shiny black PVC
which is always a good option and because the dress sits so tight there
are not many creases in the fabric it just fits very good it's almost like an
optical illusion of a two-piece outfit because the top part here looks like a
blouse especially with the hemline or not hemline seen like this I also love
the V lines here and then we have the plain skirt and we have also snap
buttons here at the arm parts and you can already see that it is a really
thick material so the form is up and standing without me doing something so
I've never tried these kind of posture collars you can already see it's really
really sturdy and thick you also have the velvet lining inside and the corset
factory branding here hope you can see that and there are three sizes so to say
so you have three options and you close it with a block but to show you this one
I'm going to change outfits I've never worn a collar like this and the name
posture color basically explains what this is about so I can't really move my
head right or left my posture is fixed the way it is I cannot really yeah look
down or up that's because it's tight and it's high so the movement is restricted
I have it in like the middle clasp here and I can swallow fine I can talk fine
but yeah it is restricting I love the color it's mixed between blue and purple
I'd say also really shiny really nice and what I also love are these three
rings here because it's a unique look they keep the o-ring in place and I think it's
cooler than just having one of these pieces here but three I paired it with this silver jumpsuit
a bit more of a fashion vibe because the color is a key piece itself and it draws the eye
if you want to see more from corset factory professional you can check out their instagram
page they also post a lot of behind the scenes and making offs they have an etsy shop and you can
also check out my video in which I introduce this brand from Turkey so yeah thanks also to
corset factory for sending me these items along really happy that I could show them on my channel
and you can leave me a comment and write what you think of the dress or the color if you like them
you can subscribe to my channel, leave a thumbs up and have a look at my Patreon for example
for behind the scenes content and I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day, bye!